http://www.prent.com/privacy-statement.cfm

Careers
Privacy Statement This Privacy Policy applies to personally identifiable information collected by Prent Corporation (“Prent”) through this web site (“the Site”) or other systems and processes under Prent’s control.
Although this Site provides links to third-party websites, they are not covered by this Privacy Policy.
Prent assumes no responsibility for the privacy or security of information you provide to any third party through linked web sites or any other means. By using this Site, you agree that you have reviewed and understood our Terms and Conditions of Use and this Privacy Policy to your full satisfaction.
You also agree that you are subject to our Terms and Conditions of Use and this Privacy Policy, and that Prent is permitted to use your personal information as set forth below. Our Privacy Policy is applicable and enforced for the Prent Corporation web site: www.prent.com.
It is our intent to comply with the European Union Data Protection Directive 95/46/EC and the Safe Harbor Guidelines of the U.S. Department of Commerce. Personal Information Prent collects information about you with respect to projects for which you may want us to issue a quote or design or when you ask us to manufacture a product.
In these situations, you are voluntarily providing information to Prent so that we can answer questions or make a project proposal.
Information required for that process may include technical and specific information about your products, your manufacturing processes and your sales and marketing requirements including images, drawings, trademarked or copyrighted digital images and logos.
We may require contact information such as name, IP address, physical address, title, department, telephone number, areas of interest and e-mail address.
In addition, when you visit our website, we may place a “cookie,” a small computer file, on your computer to help us recognize and serve you better when you return.
We keep this information to make it easier for you to use our site.
You may delete this cookie from your computer without substantially impairing your use of our site.
We also collect information submitted by job applicants. Prent uses your personal information to process your requests and transactions, offer or furnish additional products or services, personalize the types of information you receive from Prent, assess trends in the use of our site or purchases of our products or services, develop content and functionality that helps us serve our customers’ needs, and improve the service and products we provide.
Prent will not use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated in this Privacy Policy without first attempting to notify you via the most recent email address we have for you in our records. We may share your personally identifiable information with third parties that assist us in providing our services, carrying out your account needs, or providing you with information about their services that we believe may be of interest to you.
If we transfer personally identifiable information to a third party that is acting as our agent, the third party will be required to protect the confidentiality of that information.
As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets.
In any of these circumstances, personal information in our database maybe included among the transferred assets. We may use your personally identifiable information jointly with any of our related companies or subsidiaries so that they may assist us is achieving the purposes of use explained above.
Prent may also use your personal information to prevent harm or injury, to prevent fraud, to protect our legal interests, to comply with or respond to legal process, and to comply with applicable laws. Resumes and application information submitted by job applicants can be viewed by our human resources department personnel, hiring managers, employees who will be interviewing the candidate, and the administrative assistants to these individuals for applicant screening and hiring purposes, and for general human resources purposes. Choice You will have the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us when we first request your information.
Also, in our e-mail communications, you will find instructions for unsubscribing.
You can request removal of your personally identifiable information from our databases by contacting us at the address listed below or by using the [Privacy Information Request Form].
To honor your request, we will need the exact information you want removed and information sufficient for us to identify the type of communication you received from us. Data Integrity We will take reasonable steps to see that the personal information in our systems is relevant for its intended use, accurate, complete and current.
Enforcement Prent will conduct periodic reviews of compliance to verify that this Privacy Policy is accurate, comprehensive, prominently displayed, complete, implemented and accessible.
Any employee who violates this Privacy Policy may be subject to disciplinary action. Our Privacy While this website has been assembled for the purpose of informing, educating and serving our customers, the information and images on this Site are protected by applicable copyrights, trademarks, and other restrictive covenants and/or agreements and, therefore, may not be copied, downloaded, printed or used without the permission of Prent.
Special Rules Applicable to Data Collected or Processed in the European Union
This Privacy Policy applies to all personally identifiable data that is subject to the European Union’s Data Protection Directive 95/46 EC and that is transferred to the United States, even if not collected at this Site.
Prent is enrolling in the Safe Harbor System established by the U.S. Department of Commerce to meet the requirements of the European Commission’s Directive on Data Protection. Onward transfers will be permitted only to other persons or entities who have agreed to provide a continuing adequate level of protection through participation in the Safe Harbor program or one of the other mean permitted under EU Directive 95/46 EC and implementing Member State laws. If you have any concern or complaint regarding Prent’s compliance with the Safe Harbor Principles, please contact Prent where indicated below.
Prent will investigate your concern or complaint and will attempt to resolve the matter with you.
For complaints that cannot be resolved between Prent and the person making the complaint, Prent will cooperate with the European Data Protection Authorities as an independent recourse mechanism available to investigate unresolved complaints. Changes to this Policy We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time.
Please check the Policy when you use our web site to ensure that you are aware of any changes in our privacy practices.
Our Privacy Policy will indicate the date it was last updated. Governing Law The laws of the state of Wisconsin will govern any dispute involving Prent’s Privacy Policy without regard to any other state’s law regarding conflict of laws. Contact Points Please contact us to learn more about our privacy practices or to change your privacy choices: 	Privacy Manager
Prent Corporation
2225 Kennedy Road
Janesville, WI 53547-0471 Effective Date:
2225 Kennedy Rd. • P.O. Box 471 • Janesville, WI 53547-0471 • U.S.A. • TEL: 608.754.0276
